Go Big. Go Holmes.
Enola Holmes 2 is a adventure, mystery, crime film directed by Harry Bradbeer.
Now a detective-for-hire like her infamous brother, Enola Holmes takes on her first official case to find a missing girl, as the
sparks of a dangerous conspiracy ignite a mystery that requires the help of friends — and Sherlock himself — to unravel.
Enola Holmes, played by Millie Bobby Brown.
Sherlock Holmes, played by Henry Cavill.
Grail, played by David Thewlis.
Lord Tewkesbury, played by Louis Partridge.
Edith, played by Susan Wokoma.
Lestrade, played by Adeel Akhtar.
Enola Holmes 2 is a 2022 mystery film and the sequel to the 2020 film Enola Holmes, both of which star Millie Bobby Brown as the title
character, the teenage sister of the already-famous Victorian-era detective Sherlock Holmes (portrayed by Henry Cavill).
The film is directed by Harry Bradbeer from a screenplay by Jack Thorne that
adapts the book series The Enola Holmes Mysteries by Nancy Springer.
Unlike the film's predecessor, it does not adapt one of Springer's novels and
instead takes real-life inspiration from the matchgirls' strike.
In addition to Brown and Cavill, Louis Partridge, Susie Wokoma, Adeel Akhtar, and Helena Bonham Carter
reprise their supporting roles while David Thewlis and Sharon Duncan-Brewster join the cast.
Filming began in Autumn 2021 and ended in January 2022.
Enola Holmes 2 was released on Netflix on November 4, 2022.
The film received positive reviews from critics and topped
Netflix's viewership charts in 93 countries.
A third film is in production.
The film explores themes of detective, victorian england,
sequel, female detective, sherlock holmes.
The tone is mind_bending.